

ONTACT

- +88 01741748825
- rana120691@gmail.com
- Mulna, Bangladesh



Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Indesign

Microsoft Word

Microsoft Excel

Microsoft Powerpoint

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

Javascript

S LANGUAGE

- English
- Bangali (Native)

MD. REJOYAN MAMUN RANA

Graphic Designer

ABOUT ME

My name is Md. Rejoyan Mamun Rana. I'm a professional graphic designer with experience of Over 5 Years in the industry. I am experienced in Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator and Indesign. I'll provide you quality work and I'll Complete Your work as soon as possible, My first Priority is your satisfaction.

Hopefully, I will get an opportunity to work with you. If you are interested in my Skills then please contact me. I'm ready to start my job.

EDUCATION

MASTERS OF SOCIAL SECIENCE

2013-2015

Dhaka University, Bangladesh.

DIPLOMA IN GRAPHIC DESIGN

2022-2023

Daffodil Technical Institute.

EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER 01/01/2021 - 31/12/2024

Newtech Printers,

Dhaka, Bangladesh

 Designed visually compelling graphics, branding materials, social media, collaborat with creative solutions for print and digital campaigns.

 Utilized industry-standard software such as (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign) to produce high-quality designs.

Created engaging layouts, logos, and illustrations aligned with brand guidelines. etc

COMPUTER OPERATOR 01/01/2020 - 31/12/2020

Design Point

Dhaka, Bangladesh

 Performed data entry, processing, and backup tasks to business operations.

Managed and updated records, reports, and logs related to system performance and errors.

Maintained confidentiality of sensitive information while handling data processing tasks.